[{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975278533,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":21858,"timeElapsed":425706},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975282982,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":4448,"timeElapsed":430155},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975288852,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":5869,"timeElapsed":436025},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975373266,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":84413,"timeElapsed":520439},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975380116,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":6849,"timeElapsed":527289},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975387184,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":7066,"timeElapsed":534357},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975391933,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4748,"timeElapsed":539106},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975395733,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":3799,"timeElapsed":542906},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975398800,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3065,"timeElapsed":545973},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975450367,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":50483,"timeElapsed":597540},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975453801,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3433,"timeElapsed":600974},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975464736,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":10934,"timeElapsed":611909},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975471767,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":7030,"timeElapsed":618940},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975506367,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":34600,"timeElapsed":653540},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975513153,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":6785,"timeElapsed":660326},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975516284,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3130,"timeElapsed":663457},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975532852,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":16567,"timeElapsed":680025},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975535851,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2997,"timeElapsed":683024},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975538717,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2865,"timeElapsed":685890},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975577201,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":16864,"timeElapsed":724374},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975582968,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":5766,"timeElapsed":730140},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975633754,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":50786,"timeElapsed":780927},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975645851,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":12096,"timeElapsed":793024},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975648668,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2816,"timeElapsed":795841},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975719035,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":70367,"timeElapsed":866208},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975721418,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":2382,"timeElapsed":868591},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975725802,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":4382,"timeElapsed":872975},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975728039,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":2236,"timeElapsed":875212},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975740322,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":11065,"timeElapsed":887495},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975742822,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2498,"timeElapsed":889995},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975748052,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":5229,"timeElapsed":895225},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975752388,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":4335,"timeElapsed":899561},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975755336,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2945,"timeElapsed":902509},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975757920,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2583,"timeElapsed":905093},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975759853,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":1931,"timeElapsed":907025},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975762235,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2382,"timeElapsed":909408},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975764424,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"71","question":"If you could live somebody else’s life for a day, whose would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":2187,"timeElapsed":911597},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975775520,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":9816,"timeElapsed":922693},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975779253,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3732,"timeElapsed":926425},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975784656,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":5403,"timeElapsed":931829},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975787469,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":2811,"timeElapsed":934642},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975789669,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":2199,"timeElapsed":936842},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975792039,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":2369,"timeElapsed":939212},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975795424,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":3383,"timeElapsed":942596},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975797269,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":1844,"timeElapsed":944442},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975799969,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":2699,"timeElapsed":947142},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975825470,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":9828,"timeElapsed":972643},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975827369,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":1899,"timeElapsed":974542},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975831303,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3932,"timeElapsed":978476},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975834320,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3016,"timeElapsed":981493},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975836336,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2016,"timeElapsed":983509},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975838440,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2102,"timeElapsed":985612},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975840372,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":1931,"timeElapsed":987545},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975843455,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3081,"timeElapsed":990628},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975845403,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"59","question":"If you could live anywhere in the world irrespective of cost, where would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":1947,"timeElapsed":992576},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975870487,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":12933,"timeElapsed":1017660},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975873104,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2616,"timeElapsed":1020277},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975878787,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5682,"timeElapsed":1025960},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975883207,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4419,"timeElapsed":1030380},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975885803,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2595,"timeElapsed":1032976},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975891403,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":5599,"timeElapsed":1038576},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975894537,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3132,"timeElapsed":1041710},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975897240,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2702,"timeElapsed":1044413},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975900004,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2762,"timeElapsed":1047177},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975902553,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2549,"timeElapsed":1049726},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975916456,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":12801,"timeElapsed":1063629},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975919174,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":2716,"timeElapsed":1066347},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975922137,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":2962,"timeElapsed":1069310},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975925254,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3115,"timeElapsed":1072427},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975927520,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2266,"timeElapsed":1074693},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975929407,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1885,"timeElapsed":1076580},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975931470,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2063,"timeElapsed":1078643},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975933674,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2202,"timeElapsed":1080847},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975936787,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3112,"timeElapsed":1083960},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975961523,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":23401,"timeElapsed":1108696},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975964041,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2516,"timeElapsed":1111214},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734976000354,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":36312,"timeElapsed":1147527},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734976002655,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2300,"timeElapsed":1149828},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734976005038,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2382,"timeElapsed":1152211},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734976008708,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3669,"timeElapsed":1155881},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734976011237,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2528,"timeElapsed":1158410},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734976013521,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2283,"timeElapsed":1160694},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734976015625,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2102,"timeElapsed":1162798},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734976024605,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":8146,"timeElapsed":1171778},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734976027690,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3085,"timeElapsed":1174863},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734976030288,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2596,"timeElapsed":1177461},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734976033604,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3315,"timeElapsed":1180777},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734976035941,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2335,"timeElapsed":1183114},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734976038458,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2515,"timeElapsed":1185631},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734976040671,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2211,"timeElapsed":1187844},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734976044221,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3549,"timeElapsed":1191394},{"subjectID":"3czla2rtoq","prolificID":"670d2513894d1c633eeb11a6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d69500e2696170a1148","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734976046538,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2315,"timeElapsed":1193711}]